SETH MACK

+44 7508829770 <u>SETHVMACK@GMAIL.CO.UK</u> <u>LINKEDIN</u>

ABOUT

I am a Computer Science student at Imperial College London with 6 months of professional coding experience. I have a strong background in Java (specifically writing web crawlers) and experience writing production code on a shared codebase. My key abilities are picking up skills quickly and working within a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Java Developer: Wine-Searcher

[Jan 2022 - June 2022]

I worked full-time as a Java developer, for six months, writing and maintaining web crawlers for the company. In this role, I began by teaching myself the relevant skills, which resulted in me training three other employees. During my time, I promoted and implemented the use of git and GitHub in the London team.

JPMorgan Chase Software Engineering Virtual Experience

[Aug 2022]

I undertook a weeklong virtual experience project, where I completed a task in python in which I developed an alternative way to visualize and analyze data for JPMorgan traders. This task helped me develop my python knowledge and apply skills to a real-world application.

Tutoring [Aug 2019 – March 2022]

I completed Mathematics and Chemistry tutoring for over 2 years. This experience helped me develop my communication skills with people of all ages.

EDUCATION

Computing (BEng), Imperial College London

[Sep 2022 – Present]

Modules: Java Programming, Haskell Programming, C Programming, Databases, Algorithms and graphs, Computer systems, Linear Algebra, Discrete Mathematics and Calculus

Alleyn's School [Sep 2017 – July 2021]

A-Levels: A*A*A* in Mathematics, Further Mathematics, Chemistry, Physics

GCSEs: Achieved 10 9s (A*s)

SKILLS + TOOLS

Java (+700hr) - Java developer for 6 months, completed a 200hr Java module, can implement basic-level concurrency

Python (~200hr) – I originally started coding in Python and often will complete interest projects using this language.

Haskell (~150hr) - Completed a 150hr Haskell module

Swift (~100hr) - Can create an intermediate-level functioning app within a week, certificate: Build iOS Apps with SwiftUI

GitHub - Very comfortable using Git+Github in a team project

SQL (~150hr) - I can use SQL to a standard which is sufficient for most day-to-day functions of a small business

AWS use - I used AWS every day at my previous job

Excel (Intermediate) - I have completed a 40-hour excel tutorial course

Leadership - I trained and managed a team of three employees for over six months

Bookkeeping - ACCA Introduction to Bookkeeping certificate

70 wpm Touch Typing speed

Full Clean Driving License